&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：相同的类语法。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: The same class syntax.
但这就像糖下面的东西，这就是代码的样子。
But this is like the underneath the sugar, this is what the code would look like.
这是老式的原型课，也就是所谓的。
This is the old school way of doing a prototypal class, so called.
你注意到我们有一个车间功能，它将提供某种
You notice that we have a workshop function which is going to serve sort of
构造函数的用途。
the purpose of the constructor.
然后我们开始向Workshop.prototype添加方法，然后
And then we start adding methods to the Workshop.prototype, and
我们打新电话什么的。
we cog new calls and stuff.
所以你看到了一些课程的基础，但是
So you see some of the underpinnings of classes, but
这是在糖类中正在发生的事情下面的管道。
this is the plumbing underneath what is happening in the class sugar.
这并不是说你真的会写这段代码，因为如果你想这样做
It's not that you would really write this code anymore because if you wanted to do
类，您几乎可以肯定使用的是类语法。
classes at all you almost certainly be using the class syntax.
您不会再编写这个原型代码了，但我认为这对
You wouldn't write this prototypal code anymore, but I think it's important for
让你了解这个管道是如何工作的。
you to understand how this plumbing works.
关系在哪里？
Where are the relationships?
这些联系都在哪里？
Where are all of those linkages?
因为它们不是复制品，而且复印实际上是一种糟糕的心理模型，
Since they're not copies and since copying is actually a bad mental model,
我们需要一个不同的心智模型来帮助我们理解班级是如何工作的，如何
we need a different mental model that helps us understand how class works, how
它真的起作用了，所以我们可以理解当它坏了的时候，它为什么会坏掉？
it really works, so that we can understand when it breaks, why did it break?
为什么它会做一些与我们预期不同的事情呢？
Why did it do something different than what we expected?